but he's talking to an insurance advisor
the advisor tells him about the
importance of health insurance but my
lease refuses saying that his family is
fit and fine while going back home
Mahesh disease the latest mobile
advertisement outside a mobile shop and
feels tempted to buy it and ends up
buying the costly phone on monthly am
eyes relations highly stressful job and
busy working hours don't give him much
time to spend with his family he has
taken a day off did spend time with his
family
suddenly by relaxing at home and talking
to his wife
Mahesh starts feeling uneasy he tries
hard to say something to his wife but he
suddenly loses consciousness after
looking at the hospital bill Mahesh
realises that the amount is far more
than he expected
being a bill of this amount would
disturb his financial expenses for the
next few months he now realizes that
instead of buying a mobile phone he
should have invested can I help
insurance which would have helped him in
a situation like this
liya is a precious gift full of
anxieties studies reveal that medical
inflation will rise by 15 percent every
year so by 10 years the cost of heart
surgery will rise three times than today
studies conducted in the year 2016
suggest that nearly 29 people suffer
from heart attack every year 25 percent
deaths happen in the age group between
25 to 29 years
one person is killed due to heart attack
every 33 seconds and about 4 crore
Indians suffer from heart disease what
if you don't have sufficient funds in
your saving account to pay the hospital
bill
then you need to either break your bank
empties or get a loan against goal
Apollo money for firms and relatives how
many times we
to make such adjustments don't decision
to enlist in a health insurance now but
secure your family's future today and
tomorrow invest in health insurance now